const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "If 3x + 5 = 20, find x",
    options: ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
    answer: "5"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "20% of 150 = ?",
    options: ["25", "30", "35", "40"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Find next number: 2,4,8,16,?",
    options: ["18", "24", "30", "32"],
    answer: "32"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "A train 100m passes pole in 10s. Speed?",
    options: ["10 m/s", "15 m/s", "20 m/s", "25 m/s"],
    answer: "10 m/s"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "If A:B=2:3 and B:C=4:5 then A:C?",
    options: ["8:15", "6:5", "5:8", "3:4"],
    answer: "8:15"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Odd one out",
    options: ["2", "3", "5", "9"],
    answer: "9"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Simplify: (6+2)*3",
    options: ["18", "20", "22", "24"],
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Find average of 2,4,6,8",
    options: ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
    answer: "5"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Next: 1,1,2,3,5,?",
    options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
    answer: "8"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "LCM of 4 and 6?",
    options: ["10", "12", "14", "18"],
    answer: "12"
  },
];

export default questions;
